# Salagean Ionut-Cosmin

JUNIOR JAVA DEVELOPER

#### ABOUT ME

I consider myself a creative person. I am also energetic, innovative, organized, hardworking, ambitious. I like challenges. I do have a good sense of humor, but I take my work seriously. I have some basic experience in IT but I am willing to learn. Recently I finished the "Java from Scratch" course and I really like it.



#### EDUCATION

#### Software Development Academy

Java from Scratch (378 hours) | Apr 2019 - Jan 2020

- # Java # GIT # Coding
- # Software Testing TDD # Databases SQL, NoSQL
- # JDBC, Hibernate, MongoDB Java Driver
- # HTTP # Server Basics # HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- # JSP and Servlets # Introduction to JVM
- # Spring Framework # Scrum Methodology

#### Tehnical University, Cluj-Napoca

Management of modern electricity systems | Oct 2016- Jun 2018

# Tehnical University, Cluj-Napoca

Energetic engineer | Oct 2012 - Jun 2016

#### High School "Liviu Rebreanu", Turda

High School: Mathematics and computer science | Sep 2008 - Jun 2012

# HOW TO CONTACT ME

- City: Turda
- Email:
  - salagean.ionutcosmin@yahoo.com
- Phone: 0746255847
- LinkedIn:
  - https://www.linkedin.com/in/ionu%C 8%9B-cosmin-
  - s%C4%83I%C4%83gean-56767816b/
- Github:
  - https://github.com/SalageanIonutCosmin

# TECHNOLOGICAL SKILLS

- Programming Skills: Java, HTML, MvSOL
- MS Office: Word, Excel, Powerpoint, Outlook
- Electrical Engineering Skills: AutoCad, Eplan Electric

#### LANGUAGES

English - Medium

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### **Electrical Engineer**

Electrogrup S.A, Cluj-Napoca | May 2017 - present

#### Responsibilities:

- -Studying, observing and implementing the requirements from the specifications offered by the client.
- Drawing up the project for the approval stage and then for the production stage.
- Supervising the project in the execution phase.
- Drawing up the product map of the project.

#### **Acquired skills:**

- -Problem-Solving
- -Critical Thinking
- -Basic Circuit Knowledge
- -Communication Skills
- -Organisational Skills
- -Creative Thinking Skills

#### Electrician

Arcanoid Prodcom.SRL | Aug 2016 - May 2017

#### Responsibilities:

- Equip the cabinets according to the drawing.
- Wiring the cabinets according to the electrical diagrams.
- Correction any errors found in the testing of cabinets.

#### **Acquired skills:**

- Understanding electrical schemes.
- Organisational Skills.

#### Internship

Energobit S.A, Cluj-Napoca | Jun 2014 - Jul 2014

#### Responsibilities:

- Drawing up a list of all the signals and commands in the project.
- Drawing up a list of materials
- Creating an electrical circuit according to an electrical scheme.

#### Acquired skills:

- Understanding the basis of the SCADA protocol.

#### HOBBIES

- I like to play football,volley-ball.
- I like skiing, skating

## DRIVING LICENSE

- Category B